sinfulcall.com 2014-07-02

# SinfulCall

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or use our search form. When you register, we will ask you to submit your e-mail address and other personal information that we will handle discreetly and privately. You may, however, visit our site anonymously as well. By using the Service you accept the policies and conditions of the Service. This Privacy Policy is available for reference on our site.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * **To personalize your experience**  
your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs
  * **To improve our website**  
we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and **** feedback we receive from you
  * **To improve customer service**  
your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs
  * **To identify our registered users**
  * **To settle debates and issues arising during the use of the Service**
  * **For marketing purposes** with the consent of our users during the use of the Service, until the withdrawal of user consent and only for the purposes of data process of such nature  

We will not call you or e-mail you on a regular basis (only if you agree to), however, the phone number and/or e-mail address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional updates, related information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future e-mails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each e-mail.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We are committed to handling your information responsibly and with respect. We offer the use of a secure server.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your browser - if you allow - that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties, who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Log files

Like many other websites, [www.sinfulcall.com](http://www.sinfulcall.com/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Children's online privacy protection act compliance

We do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years (21 years in some countries and states) of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years (or 21 years) old or older.

### Protecting minors

We take enhanced security measures in order to protect minors from visiting our site. We are members of the ASACP, and we recommend the use of [www.netnanny.com](http://www.netnanny.com/) or [www.cyberpatrol.com](http://www.cyberpatrol.com/)’s solutions in order to protect underage internet users.

### Online privacy policy only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Terms of Use

Please also visit our Terms of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

### Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an e-mail notifying you of any changes.
